United University Professions (UUP); Records apap039
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
- Office of the Secretary, 1968-1999; IV; 61.73 cubic ft.
  - Subject Files [RESTRICTED], 1967-March 1993; 1977-1988; 7; 7.33 cubic ft.
    This series primarily includes correspondence, UUP-produced materials, and third-party reports and publications. Correspondents include UUP's President, Secretary, Vice Presidents, and occasionally UUP's Director of Staff. The recipients include chapter leadership, individual members, representatives of other higher education and labor organizations. Among the materials that date back to the Wakshull administration, some infrequently include handwritten notes that may be those of Evelyn Hartman, UUP's Executive Director during the Wakshull administration. To some extent, the materials in this series are slightly more administrative to UUP's operations than those included in the project and subject files of Presidents Wakshull, Drescher, and Reilly in series 3, 4, and 5 of Subgroup III. For example, this series includes materials relating to UUP's incorporation and dissolution as a corporate entity, correspondence between UUP, Hartford Life, and Metropolitan Life Insurance Company regarding the excess major medical and group life insurance UUP provides for its members; correspondence regarding lending UUP phone lines to NYSUT, setting up a credit union for UUP's administrative office staff, and some agreements and correspondence with the Communications Workers of America (CWA) which represents UUP's clerical staff. The series also includes such reference materials as agency fee procedures, PDQWL grant application forms, and the policies of the SUNY Board of Trustees for a number of years. No one topic is particularly focused on, although the amount of materials for each subject varies widely. The lobbying materials include handwritten lobbying reports made by UUP members on lobbying days reporting which legislators (or their staff) they met with and their reactions to UUU's concerns.
    - Accuracy in Academia organization [RESTRICTED], 1985 November-1986 March (Box IV.7.1 (IV-Office of the Secretary), Folder 1)
    - Advertising [RESTRICTED], 1979 June-1979 August; 1982 January (Box IV.7.1 (IV-Office of the Secretary), Folder 2)
    - Aetna-UUP 403(b) Tax Deferred Annuity [RESTRICTED], 1986 March-1986 October (Box IV.7.1 (IV-Office of the Secretary), Folder 3)
    - Affirmative Action [RESTRICTED], 1978 Fall-1979 April (Box IV.7.1 (IV-Office of the Secretary), Folder 4)
    - Affirmative Action [RESTRICTED], 1979 July-1988 October (Box IV.7.1 (IV-Office of the Secretary), Folder 5)
    - AFL-CIO (national and NY State) [RESTRICTED], 1978 March-1985 February (Box IV.7.1 (IV-Office of the Secretary), Folder 6)
    - AFL-CIO (national and NY State) [RESTRICTED], 1985 March-1987 May (Box IV.7.1 (IV-Office of the Secretary), Folder 7)
    - AFL-CIO (national and NY State) [RESTRICTED], 1987 June-1989 November (Box IV.7.1 (IV-Office of the Secretary), Folder 8)
    - AFL-CIO (national and NY State) [RESTRICTED], 1989 September-1991 November (Box IV.7.1 (IV-Office of the Secretary), Folder 9)
    - AFT [RESTRICTED], 1985 January-1986 March (Box IV.7.1 (IV-Office of the Secretary), Folder 10)
    - AFT [RESTRICTED], 1986 April-1986 December (Box IV.7.1 (IV-Office of the Secretary), Folder 11)
    - AFT [RESTRICTED], 1987 January-1992 August (Box IV.7.1 (IV-Office of the Secretary), Folder 12)
    - AFT Distinguished Teacher Fellowship Program [RESTRICTED], 1986 June (Box IV.7.1 (IV-Office of the Secretary), Folder 13)
    - AFT Faculty Federation Board of Governors [RESTRICTED], 1978 March-1989 March (Box IV.7.1 (IV-Office of the Secretary), Folder 14)
    - AFT Full Membership Program [RESTRICTED], 1989-1990 (Box IV.7.1 (IV-Office of the Secretary), Folder 15)
    - AFT Group Insurance Plans [RESTRICTED], 1979 October-1980 May (Box IV.7.1 (IV-Office of the Secretary), Folder 16)
    - AFT Task Force on the Future of Education [RESTRICTED], 1986 June (Box IV.7.1 (IV-Office of the Secretary), Folder 17)
    - Ag & Tech Dinner [RESTRICTED], 1984 August-1984 September (Box IV.7.1 (IV-Office of the Secretary), Folder 18)
    - Agency Fee [RESTRICTED], 1972-1988; 3 folders (Box IV.7.1 (IV-Office of the Secretary), Folder 19-21)
    - Agency Fee [RESTRICTED], 1987 June-1989 May (Box IV.7.1 (IV-Office of the Secretary), Folder 22)
    - Agency Fee-Director of State Payroll Audit [RESTRICTED], 1977 September-1984 August (Box IV.7.1 (IV-Office of the Secretary), Folder 23)
    - Agency Fee Fiscal Year 1980-81 [RESTRICTED], 1982 January-1982 July (Box IV.7.1 (IV-Office of the Secretary), Folder 24)
    - Agency Fee Fiscal Year 1981-1982 [RESTRICTED], 1982 June-1983 February (Box IV.7.1 (IV-Office of the Secretary), Folder 25)
    - Agency Fee-Insurance/Eson case [RESTRICTED], 1982 March-1982 July (Box IV.7.1 (IV-Office of the Secretary), Folder 26)
    - Agency Fee-Rebate Procedures [RESTRICTED], 1985-1986; 1986-1987 (Box IV.7.1 (IV-Office of the Secretary), Folder 27)
    - AIDS [RESTRICTED], 1983 July-1985 November (Box IV.7.1 (IV-Office of the Secretary), Folder 28)
    - AIDS [RESTRICTED], 1985 December-1990 October (Box IV.7.1 (IV-Office of the Secretary), Folder 29)
    - American Association of University Professors (AAUP) [RESTRICTED], 1977 April-1978 November (Box IV.7.1 (IV-Office of the Secretary), Folder 30)
    - American Association of University Professors (AAUP) [RESTRICTED], 1981 March-1988 March (Box IV.7.1 (IV-Office of the Secretary), Folder 31)
    - Asbestos-Assembly Task Force on Asbestos [RESTRICTED], 1986 September (Box IV.7.1 (IV-Office of the Secretary), Folder 32)
    - Assembly-New York State [RESTRICTED], 1985-1986 (Box IV.7.1 (IV-Office of the Secretary), Folder 33)
    - Association of Pennsylvania State College and University Faculties [RESTRICTED], 1975 June-1976 April; 1984 March-1988 November (Box IV.7.2 (IV-Office of the Secretary), Folder 1)
    - Baldwin, James, Conference and Workshop [RESTRICTED], 1985 Spring (Box IV.7.2 (IV-Office of the Secretary), Folder 2)
    - Benefits [RESTRICTED], 1983 October-1985 December (Box IV.7.2 (IV-Office of the Secretary), Folder 3)
    - Benefits [RESTRICTED], 1986 January-1986 August (Box IV.7.2 (IV-Office of the Secretary), Folder 4)
    - Benefits [RESTRICTED], 1986 September-1988 August (Box IV.7.2 (IV-Office of the Secretary), Folder 5)
    - Blue Cross/Blue Shield [RESTRICTED], 1978 March-1978 May (Box IV.7.2 (IV-Office of the Secretary), Folder 6)
    - Board of Regents, NY State Education Department [RESTRICTED], 1980 September (Box IV.7.2 (IV-Office of the Secretary), Folder 7)
    - Board of Regents, NY State Education Department [RESTRICTED], 1981 February-1983 December (Box IV.7.2 (IV-Office of the Secretary), Folder 8)
    - Board of Regents, NY State Education Department [RESTRICTED], 1984 May-1987 July (Box IV.7.2 (IV-Office of the Secretary), Folder 9)
    - Board of Trustees (SUNY) Policies [RESTRICTED], 1967; 1968; 1970; 1972-1977 (Box IV.7.2 (IV-Office of the Secretary), Folder 10)
    - Board of Trustees (SUNY) Policies [RESTRICTED], 1980-1981; 1989 (Box IV.7.2 (IV-Office of the Secretary), Folder 11)
    - Budget Analysis Task Force [RESTRICTED], 1984 October-1985 May (Box IV.7.2 (IV-Office of the Secretary), Folder 12)
    - Budget Cuts [RESTRICTED], 1979 December-1980 September (Box IV.7.2 (IV-Office of the Secretary), Folder 13)
    - Budget-New York State 1985-86 Impact on Campuses [RESTRICTED], 1985 January-1985 April (Box IV.7.2 (IV-Office of the Secretary), Folder 14)
    - Budget-New York State [RESTRICTED], 1986 January-1989 January (Box IV.7.2 (IV-Office of the Secretary), Folder 15)
    - Budget-UUP, proposed 1982-1983 [RESTRICTED], 1982 Spring (Box IV.7.2 (IV-Office of the Secretary), Folder 16)
    - Budget-UUP 1982-83 and 1981-82 [RESTRICTED] (Box IV.7.2 (IV-Office of the Secretary), Folder 17)
    - Bundy Aid [RESTRICTED], 1982 May-1987 September (Box IV.7.2 (IV-Office of the Secretary), Folder 18)
    - Career Alternative Program (NYSUT workshop for retrenchees) [RESTRICTED], 1981 July-1982 February (Box IV.7.2 (IV-Office of the Secretary), Folder 19)
    - Carnegie Report, "A National Prepared: Teachers for the 21st Century"/Teacher Education Task Force [RESTRICTED], 1986 February-1986 November (Box IV.7.2 (IV-Office of the Secretary), Folder 20)
    - Challenge 1981 (NEA/NYEA) [RESTRICTED], 1981 March-1981 April (Box IV.7.2 (IV-Office of the Secretary), Folder 21)
    - Clients' Security Fund of the State of New York [RESTRICTED], 1983 April (Box IV.7.2 (IV-Office of the Secretary), Folder 22)
    - Clinical Practice Plan [RESTRICTED], 1977 April-1980 July (Box IV.7.2 (IV-Office of the Secretary), Folder 23)
    - Clinical Practice Plan [RESTRICTED], 1980 September-1986 October (Box IV.7.2 (IV-Office of the Secretary), Folder 24)
    - Clinical Practice Plan [RESTRICTED], 1987 March (Box IV.7.2 (IV-Office of the Secretary), Folder 25)
    - Clinical Practice Plan [RESTRICTED], 1987 April-1987 September (Box IV.7.2 (IV-Office of the Secretary), Folder 26)
    - Clinical Practice-Buffalo Dentists [RESTRICTED], 1983 June-1983 November (Box IV.7.2 (IV-Office of the Secretary), Folder 27)
    - Clinical Practice-Buffalo MDs [RESTRICTED], 1983 June-1984 July (Box IV.7.2 (IV-Office of the Secretary), Folder 28)
    - Clinical Practice-Downstate [RESTRICTED], 1983 May-1985 May (Box IV.7.2 (IV-Office of the Secretary), Folder 29)
    - Clinical Practice-Optometry [RESTRICTED], 1983 May-1983 December (Box IV.7.2 (IV-Office of the Secretary), Folder 30)
    - Coalition Against Layoffs [RESTRICTED], 1983 February (Box IV.7.2 (IV-Office of the Secretary), Folder 31)
    - Coalition for Public Higher Education [RESTRICTED], 1979-1981; 3 folders (Box IV.7.3 (IV-Office of the Secretary), Folder 1-3)
    - Commission on Independent Colleges and Universities (cIcu) [RESTRICTED], 1981 October-1985 February (Box IV.7.3 (IV-Office of the Secretary), Folder 4)
    - Contract Ratification Votes (American Arbitration Association) [RESTRICTED], 1986 May-1988 August (Box IV.7.3 (IV-Office of the Secretary), Folder 5)
    - Cordadian Corp. (office telephone) [RESTRICTED], 1988 September (Box IV.7.3 (IV-Office of the Secretary), Folder 6)
    - Cornell University-NY State School of Industrial and Labor Relations [RESTRICTED], 1983 December-1988 February (Box IV.7.3 (IV-Office of the Secretary), Folder 7)
    - Cozort, William [RESTRICTED], 1981 May-1990 August (Box IV.7.3 (IV-Office of the Secretary), Folder 8)
    - Credit Union [RESTRICTED], 1985 February (Box IV.7.3 (IV-Office of the Secretary), Folder 9)
    - CSEA [RESTRICTED], 1978 March-1988 January (Box IV.7.3 (IV-Office of the Secretary), Folder 10)
    - CWA [RESTRICTED], 1984 June-1987 March (Box IV.7.3 (IV-Office of the Secretary), Folder 11)
    - Dental Plan [RESTRICTED], 1979 (Box IV.7.3 (IV-Office of the Secretary), Folder 12)
    - Drescher, Nuala-postcards [RESTRICTED], 1984 (Box IV.7.3 (IV-Office of the Secretary), Folder 13)
    - E.F. Hutton [RESTRICTED], 1982 December-1985 October (Box IV.7.3 (IV-Office of the Secretary), Folder 14)
    - E.F. Hutton [RESTRICTED], 1985 October-1986 April (Box IV.7.3 (IV-Office of the Secretary), Folder 15)
    - ECIA Chapter 2 Advisory Committee [RESTRICTED], 1985 December (Box IV.7.3 (IV-Office of the Secretary), Folder 16)
    - Empire Plan (Health Care) [RESTRICTED], 1985 April-1988 March (Box IV.7.3 (IV-Office of the Secretary), Folder 17)
    - Empire State Institute for the Performing Arts [RESTRICTED], 1984 September; 1988 June (Box IV.7.3 (IV-Office of the Secretary), Folder 18)
    - Empire State Mathematics and Science Teacher Scholarship [RESTRICTED], 1984 November (Box IV.7.3 (IV-Office of the Secretary), Folder 19)
    - Employee Assistance Program [RESTRICTED], 1980 October-1983 October (Box IV.7.3 (IV-Office of the Secretary), Folder 20)
    - Employee Assistance Program [RESTRICTED], 1984 February-1984 September (Box IV.7.3 (IV-Office of the Secretary), Folder 21)
    - Employee Assistance Program [RESTRICTED], 1984 October-1984 December (Box IV.7.3 (IV-Office of the Secretary), Folder 22)
    - Employee Assistance Program [RESTRICTED], 1985 January-1986 March (Box IV.7.3 (IV-Office of the Secretary), Folder 23)
    - Employee Assistance Program [RESTRICTED], 1986 June-1989 January (Box IV.7.3 (IV-Office of the Secretary), Folder 24)
    - Employee Benefits Practices (newsletter of International Foundation of Employee Benefit Plans) [RESTRICTED], 1987 October (Box IV.7.3 (IV-Office of the Secretary), Folder 25)
    - Employee Pension Fund [RESTRICTED], 1986 January; 1987 December (Box IV.7.3 (IV-Office of the Secretary), Folder 26)
    - Ethics Law Exceptions-mailing to members requesting [RESTRICTED], 1989 March 10 (Box IV.7.3 (IV-Office of the Secretary), Folder 27)
    - Fair Labor Standards Act [RESTRICTED], 1985-1987; 3 folders (Box IV.7.3 (IV-Office of the Secretary), Folder 28-30)
    - Floating Holidays [RESTRICTED], 1986 September-1987 March (Box IV.7.3 (IV-Office of the Secretary), Folder 31)
    - Friend of SUNY Award [RESTRICTED], 1984 November-1988 December (Box IV.7.3 (IV-Office of the Secretary), Folder 32)
    - Galbraith, Jeanne [RESTRICTED], 1987 June-1988 June (Box IV.7.3 (IV-Office of the Secretary), Folder 33)
    - Graduate Student Employee Union [RESTRICTED], 1984 June-1985 January; 1992 April-1992 September (Box IV.7.3 (IV-Office of the Secretary), Folder 34)
    - Grievances [RESTRICTED], 1980 October-1987 March (Box IV.7.3 (IV-Office of the Secretary), Folder 35)
    - Handbook for Chapter Treasurers [RESTRICTED], 1982 April; 1982 December (Box IV.7.3 (IV-Office of the Secretary), Folder 36)
    - Hartford Life Insurance [RESTRICTED], 1981 June-1987 November (Box IV.7.3 (IV-Office of the Secretary), Folder 37)
    - Higher Education [Financial] Assistance [RESTRICTED], 1980 October-1988 March (Box IV.7.3 (IV-Office of the Secretary), Folder 38)
    - Higher Education Services Corporation (HESC New York State) [RESTRICTED], 1984 April-1987 December (Box IV.7.3 (IV-Office of the Secretary), Folder 39)
    - Historical Summaries-UUP [RESTRICTED], ca. 1979 (Box IV.7.4 (IV-Office of the Secretary), Folder 1)
    - Hospice [RESTRICTED], 1986 July-1986 August (Box IV.7.4 (IV-Office of the Secretary), Folder 1A)
    - Hospital Reorganization Consultants' Report [RESTRICTED], 1986 February-1986 April (Box IV.7.4 (IV-Office of the Secretary), Folder 2)
    - Incorporation-SPA and UUP [RESTRICTED], 1971-1974 (Box IV.7.4 (IV-Office of the Secretary), Folder 3)
    - Incorporation-UUP, Inc. Dissolution Proceedings [RESTRICTED], 1980 July-1982 July (Box IV.7.4 (IV-Office of the Secretary), Folder 4)
    - Increase in Paychecks Problem [RESTRICTED], 1986 August-1986 September (Box IV.7.4 (IV-Office of the Secretary), Folder 5)
    - Indemnification legislation [RESTRICTED], 1978 March-1982 May (Box IV.7.4 (IV-Office of the Secretary), Folder 6)
    - Independent Commission on the Future of the State University/"The Challenge and the Choice" report [RESTRICTED], 1984 June-1987 January (Box IV.7.4 (IV-Office of the Secretary), Folder 7)
    - "Innovations in Undergraduate Instruction: Model for the Nineties" (PDQWL co-sponsored conference) [RESTRICTED], 1988 February-1988 April (Box IV.7.4 (IV-Office of the Secretary), Folder 8)
    - "Inside Your Schools, The AFT Television Magazine", (NYSUT) [RESTRICTED], 1984 July-1985 February (Box IV.7.4 (IV-Office of the Secretary), Folder 9)
    - Institute for Research in History, "Scholars in Transition: From the Academy to the Marketplace" program [RESTRICTED], 1983 June-1983 October (Box IV.7.4 (IV-Office of the Secretary), Folder 10)
    - Jewish Labor Committee [RESTRICTED], 1986 February-1988 June (Box IV.7.4 (IV-Office of the Secretary), Folder 11)
    - Joint Labor Management Committees [RESTRICTED], 1985-1986; 2 folders (Box IV.7.4 (IV-Office of the Secretary), Folder 12-13)
    - Joint Labor Management Meeting/Workshop [RESTRICTED], 1989 September-1989 October (Box IV.7.4 (IV-Office of the Secretary), Folder 14)
    - Journalism Competition [RESTRICTED], 1984 March (Box IV.7.4 (IV-Office of the Secretary), Folder 15)
    - Kyvig, David (Editor Law, Alcohol and Order: Perspectives on National Prohibition, Drescher contribution: "Labor and Prohibition: The Unappreciated Impact of the Eighteenth Amendment") [RESTRICTED], 1984 June-1984 August (Box IV.7.4 (IV-Office of the Secretary), Folder 16)
    - Labor Management Meetings [RESTRICTED], 1978 April-1987 February (Box IV.7.4 (IV-Office of the Secretary), Folder 17)
    - Labor-Religion Coalition [RESTRICTED], 1984 January-1985 February; 1989 (Box IV.7.4 (IV-Office of the Secretary), Folder 18)
    - Legal (miscellaneous) [RESTRICTED], 1977 March-1987 December (Box IV.7.4 (IV-Office of the Secretary), Folder 19)
    - Legal Papers (PERB) [RESTRICTED], 1977-1978 (Box IV.7.4 (IV-Office of the Secretary), Folder 20)
    - Legislature [RESTRICTED], 1987 January-1989 March (Box IV.7.4 (IV-Office of the Secretary), Folder 21)
    - Librarians [RESTRICTED], 1986 April (Box IV.7.4 (IV-Office of the Secretary), Folder 22)
    - Lobbying [RESTRICTED], 1982-1983 (Box IV.7.4 (IV-Office of the Secretary), Folder 23)
    - Lobbying [RESTRICTED], 1984-1985 (Box IV.7.4 (IV-Office of the Secretary), Folder 24)
    - Lobbying [RESTRICTED], 1986 February-1986 March (Box IV.7.4 (IV-Office of the Secretary), Folder 25)
    - Lobbying [RESTRICTED], 1987-1988 (Box IV.7.4 (IV-Office of the Secretary), Folder 26)
    - Lobbying [RESTRICTED], 1988 February-1988 March (Box IV.7.4 (IV-Office of the Secretary), Folder 27)
    - Lobbying [RESTRICTED], 1990 March (Box IV.7.4 (IV-Office of the Secretary), Folder 28)
    - Lobbying [RESTRICTED], 1991 March (Box IV.7.4 (IV-Office of the Secretary), Folder 29)
    - Lobbying-Washington, D.C. [RESTRICTED], 1990 June (Box IV.7.4 (IV-Office of the Secretary), Folder 30)
    - Mandatory Retirement [RESTRICTED], 1985 June-1986 June (Box IV.7.4 (IV-Office of the Secretary), Folder 31)
    - Martinez, Arsenio P. (grievance) [RESTRICTED], 1983 January-1984 March (Box IV.7.4 (IV-Office of the Secretary), Folder 32)
    - Mary Muldoon Teacher Assistance Fund (NYSUT) [RESTRICTED], 1978 May (Box IV.7.4 (IV-Office of the Secretary), Folder 33)
    - Master Plan (SUNY) [RESTRICTED], 1980; 1984 (Box IV.7.4 (IV-Office of the Secretary), Folder 34)
    - Medical Emergency Procedures SUNY campuses [RESTRICTED], 1977 (Box IV.7.4 (IV-Office of the Secretary), Folder 35)
    - Medical Quadrangle, Inc. (malpractice insurance) [RESTRICTED], 1986 October-1987 August (Box IV.7.4 (IV-Office of the Secretary), Folder 36)
    - Member Benefits [RESTRICTED], 1978 May-1981 June (Box IV.7.4 (IV-Office of the Secretary), Folder 37)
    - Member Benefits [RESTRICTED], 1983 October-1985 March; 1988 February (Box IV.7.4 (IV-Office of the Secretary), Folder 38)
    - Merger-SUNY/CUNY [RESTRICTED], 1977 March; 1979 March (Box IV.7.4 (IV-Office of the Secretary), Folder 39)
    - Metropolitan Life Insurance Co. [RESTRICTED], 1989 (Box IV.7.4 (IV-Office of the Secretary), Folder 40)
    - Metropolitan Life Insurance Co. [RESTRICTED], 1990 (Box IV.7.4 (IV-Office of the Secretary), Folder 41)
    - Metropolitan Life Insurance Co. [RESTRICTED], 1991 (Box IV.7.4 (IV-Office of the Secretary), Folder 42)
    - Nassau Community College [RESTRICTED], 1984 February-1988 May (Box IV.7.4 (IV-Office of the Secretary), Folder 43)
    - National Center for the Study of Collective Bargaining in Higher Education and the Professions (Baruch College, CUNY) [RESTRICTED], 1978 April-1982 December; 1987 September-1988 October (Box IV.7.4 (IV-Office of the Secretary), Folder 44)
    - National Labor Relations Board [RESTRICTED], 1978 March; 1984 March-1984 May (Box IV.7.5 (IV-Office of the Secretary), Folder 1)
    - NEA (National Education Association) [RESTRICTED], 1973 June; 1973 November; 1976 March-1979 August (Box IV.7.5 (IV-Office of the Secretary), Folder 2)
    - New York Frontlash [RESTRICTED], 1984 September (Box IV.7.5 (IV-Office of the Secretary), Folder 3)
    - New York Library Association [RESTRICTED], 1982 April (Box IV.7.5 (IV-Office of the Secretary), Folder 4)
    - New York State Public Sector Coalition on Health Care Benefits [RESTRICTED], 1990 May (Box IV.7.5 (IV-Office of the Secretary), Folder 5)
    - New Youth Connections [RESTRICTED], 1984 December (Box IV.7.5 (IV-Office of the Secretary), Folder 6)
    - Newsletter Editors [RESTRICTED], 1983 September; 1987 March (Box IV.7.5 (IV-Office of the Secretary), Folder 7)
    - Newspaper Articles [RESTRICTED], 1978-1988 (Box IV.7.5 (IV-Office of the Secretary), Folder 8)
    - Nurse Membership [RESTRICTED], 1982 January-1982 February (Box IV.7.5 (IV-Office of the Secretary), Folder 9)
    - OSHA [RESTRICTED], 1981-1983; 2 folders (Box IV.7.5 (IV-Office of the Secretary), Folder 10-11)
    - PACE (Project for Adult College Education)/UUP Economic Development Project [RESTRICTED], 1978-1987; 4 folders (Box IV.7.5 (IV-Office of the Secretary), Folder 12-15)
    - Patent Policy/Computer Software Policy (SUNY) [RESTRICTED], 1986 October; 1987 January-1987 August (Box IV.7.5 (IV-Office of the Secretary), Folder 16)
    - PDQWL Leave Applications [RESTRICTED], 1993 January-1993 March (Box IV.7.5 (IV-Office of the Secretary), Folder 17)
    - Performance Evaluations [RESTRICTED], 1979 March-1980 March (Box IV.7.5 (IV-Office of the Secretary), Folder 18)
    - Press Releases and UUP Mailings [RESTRICTED], 1978 August-1978 December; 1982 August (Box IV.7.5 (IV-Office of the Secretary), Folder 19)
    - Professional Staff Congress [RESTRICTED], 1978 May-1984 January (Box IV.7.5 (IV-Office of the Secretary), Folder 20)
    - Professional Staff Congress [RESTRICTED], 1984 March-1988 October; 1990 January; 1993 February-1993 March (Box IV.7.5 (IV-Office of the Secretary), Folder 21)
    - Professionals [RESTRICTED], 1978 March-1981 September (Box IV.7.5 (IV-Office of the Secretary), Folder 22)
    - Public Employees Benefit Fund [RESTRICTED], 1982 October-1984 October (Box IV.7.5 (IV-Office of the Secretary), Folder 23)
    - Public Employees Benefit Fund [RESTRICTED], 1984 December-1985 May (Box IV.7.5 (IV-Office of the Secretary), Folder 24)
    - Public Employees Benefit Fund [RESTRICTED], 1985 June-1986 May (Box IV.7.5 (IV-Office of the Secretary), Folder 25)
    - Public Employees Benefit Fund [RESTRICTED], 1986 June-1987 January (Box IV.7.5 (IV-Office of the Secretary), Folder 26)
    - Public Employees Benefit Fund [RESTRICTED], 1987 February-1988 December; 1991 August (Box IV.7.5 (IV-Office of the Secretary), Folder 27)
    - Public Employees Federation [RESTRICTED], 1977 November-1988 July (Box IV.7.5 (IV-Office of the Secretary), Folder 28)
    - Public Relations [RESTRICTED], 1979 February-1987 January (Box IV.7.5 (IV-Office of the Secretary), Folder 29)
    - Reclassification [RESTRICTED], 1987 August-1987 September (Box IV.7.6 (IV-Office of the Secretary), Folder 1)
    - Reclassification [RESTRICTED], 1987 June-1988 April; 2 folders (Box IV.7.6 (IV-Office of the Secretary), Folder 2-3)
    - Reclassification (?) Teaching Hospital position descriptions [RESTRICTED], Undated (Box IV.7.6 (IV-Office of the Secretary), Folder 4)
    - Reclassification-Albany [RESTRICTED], 1987 October (Box IV.7.6 (IV-Office of the Secretary), Folder 5)
    - Reclassification-Alfred [RESTRICTED], 1987 September-1987 November (Box IV.7.6 (IV-Office of the Secretary), Folder 6)
    - Reclassification-Binghamton [RESTRICTED], 1987 October (Box IV.7.6 (IV-Office of the Secretary), Folder 7)
    - Reclassification-Brooklyn HSC [RESTRICTED], 1987 April-1987 December (Box IV.7.6 (IV-Office of the Secretary), Folder 8)